A Guide to the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial records FA061
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1917-1949; 3
  - Appropriations - Emergency Relief, 3_03
    - American Relief Administration - Russian Refugees, 1922-1924 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - American Relief Administration - Russian Refugees, 1922-1924 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - American Relief Administration - European Child Feeding, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - American Relief Administration - Medical Supplies, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      Russia.
    - China Famine Fund, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      With John D. Rockefeller, Jr. - debt.
    - Near East Relief, 1921-1928 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      Advisory Committee-LSRM. Refugees, orphans, deficit, Charles Vickery.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 2, Folders 21-22.
    - Near East Relief, 1921-1928 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Near East Relief, 1921-1928 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Near East Relief - Reports (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - "Flowsheet- Near East Relief- Indicating Sources of Income & Nature of Expenditures", 1919; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 7)
      Separated Materials note
      Larger duplicate of this is on display in Research & Education offices at RAC
    - Near East Relief - Reports (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Russian Intellectuals, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 105)
      American Relief Administration (ARA) to continue program, Student Friendship Fund to feed students. Travel and clothing - school teachers, students, professional people, Walter Lyman Brown.
    - Russian Intellectuals - Letters of Appreciation (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Russian Refugees Relief Association - London, 1921-1923 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Russian Zemstvos, 1922-1932 (Box 9, Folder 108)
      LSRM-RF. Russians abroad. Prince Lvoff, Herbert Hoover.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 2, Folder 17.
    - Russian Zemstvos, 1922-1932 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Russian Zemstvos - Reports (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Student Friendship Fund - German Relief, 1923-1929 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      Food, loans, services, general background information.
    - Student Friendship Fund - Russian Relief, 1923-1926 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      LSRM-RF. Food, medicine, books, and journals. Herbert Hoover.
    - Student Friendship Fund - Russian Relief, 1923-1926 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Student Friendship Fund - Russian Relief - Exhibits (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Student Friendship Fund - Russian Relief - Exhibits (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Student Friendship Fund - General Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Appropriations - Leisure, 3_04
    - American Association of Museums, 1922-1928 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      General background information, Frederic Allen Whiting.
    - American Association of Museums - Park Education Survey, 1926-1929 (Box 11, Folder 118)
      Study and outline of future educational program of the National Parks through Secretary of the Interior.
    - American Association of Museums - Trailside, 1926-1929 (Box 11, Folder 119)
      Educational program. Demonstration and experiment. One at Grand Canyon, other at Palisades. Hubert Work. Stephen Mather.
    - American Association of Museums - Yellowstone, 1927-1932 (Box 11, Folder 120)
      LSRM-RF. Popular education. Adult education in parks and survey of educational work. Main building and trailside branch. H. C. Bumpus, Ray Lyman Wilbur.
    - American Association of Museums - Yosemite, 1924-1927 (Box 11, Folder 121)
      Educational museum. Ansel Hall.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 2, Folder 18.
    - American Association of Museums - Yosemite, 1924-1927 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - American Museum of Natural History - Ruml Report, 1921-1922 (Box 11, Folder 123)
      RF survey.
    - American Physical Education Association, 1923-1928 (Box 11, Folder 124)
      Clearing house, physical efficiency test, report on gym standards.
    - Boy Scout Foundation of Greater New York, 1922-1925 (Box 11, Folder 125)
      Budget, promotional work, scouting masters.
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1919-1922 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life, 1922-1925 (Box 11, Folder 127)
      LSRM-RF, magazine, trust.
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life, 1922-1925 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life, 1927-1943 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life, 1927-1943 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life - Agreements (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Boy's Life - Trust Fund, 1920-1932 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Boy's Conservation Bureau, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Camp Fire Girls, 1923-1928 (Box 12, Folder 134)
      Educational program for leaders' emergency grant for fire replacement.
    - Camp Fire Girls, 1923-1928 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Community Service, 1919-1922 (Box 12, Folder 136)
      Wholesome recreation and social activity in industrial cities, general background information.
    - Coordinating Council in Nature Activities, 1927-1930 (Box 12, Folder 137)
      LSRM-RF. With American Museum of Natural History, general background information.
    - Federated Societies, 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 138)
      Organization of cities and regional planning, preservation of national parks and scenic assets, general background information.
    - Federated Societies - State Park Survey, 1925-1928 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Girl Scouts - Manhattan, 1921-1925 (Box 13, Folder 140)
    - Girl Scouts - National, 1920-1928 (Box 13, Folder 141)
      General background information, research bureau, extension, education.
    - Girl Scouts - National, 1920-1928 (Box 13, Folder 142)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 143)
      LSRM-RF. Acquisition of land for national park in Tennessee and North Carolina. Little River Lumber Company and Suncrest Lumber Company controversy. Arno Cammerer, Jr.
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 144)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 145)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 146)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 148)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund, 1926-1938 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Great Smokey Mountain Memorial Fund - clippings and pamphlets (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1921-1928 (Box 14, Folder 151)
      Museum study; endowment, space, educational work.
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Charts (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - National Amateur Athletic Federation, 1922-1928 (Box 14, Folder 153)
      Advisory Committee-LSRM. High standards, promote amateur interests, general background information.
    - National Amateur Athletic Federation, 1922-1928 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - National Amateur Athletic Federation, 1922-1928 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - National Amateur Athletic Federation - Pamphlets (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1924-1930 (Box 14, Folder 157)
      LSRM-RF. General background information, special studies, projects, and surveys to develop a national policy on outdoor recreation; clearing house.
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1924-1930 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1924-1930 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1924-1930 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation - Federal Lands Survey, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 161)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation - Kirby Survey, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 162)
      Industrial recreation.
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation - National Parks Survey, 1924-1927 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation - State Park Survey, 1924-1929 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - National Museum of Engineering and Industry, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - New York Botanical Garden, 1923-1925 (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - New York Botanical Garden - Reports (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - New York Community Service, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 168)
      Character making recreation and leisure time, general background information.
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1919-1924 (Box 15, Folder 169)
      Steamboats, endowment, camps, park study, George Perkins.
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1919-1924 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1925-1937 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1925-1937 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Report, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 172A)
    - Parks and Playgrounds Association of New York, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1921-1925 (Box 16, Folder 174)
      LSRM-RF. Provide recreation and advance legislation for recreational work, advise, train leaders; general background information.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1921-1925 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1921-1925 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1926-1940 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1926-1940 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1926-1940 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1926-1940 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America, 1926-1940 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Pamphlets (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Reports (Box 17, Folder 183)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Reports (Box 17, Folder 184)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - City Parks Study, 1924-1928 (Box 18, Folder 185)
      Nationwide survey of municipal and county statutes, standards, and suggestions.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - City Parks Study, 1924-1928 (Box 18, Folder 186)
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Community Music, 1928-1932 (Box 18, Folder 187)
      LSRM-RF. Music teachers for small towns.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Community School, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 188)
      Chicago - training for leaders in recreation.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Investigations, 1925-1929 (Box 18, Folder 189)
      Test results of data gathered of 25 years.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Music Study, 1926-1934 (Box 18, Folder 190)
      LSRM-RF. Community music throughout the country.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Recreational Advisor, 1926-1930 (Box 18, Folder 191)
      LSRM-RF. New York City Mayor's office.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Summer Camps, 1923-1931 (Box 18, Folder 192)
      LSRM-RF Handbook.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Vacation Service Bureau, 1924-1930 (Box 18, Folder 193)
      LSRM-RF. Preliminary study.
    - Playground and Recreation Association of America - Vacation Service Bureau, 1924-1930 (Box 18, Folder 194)
    - Public School Athletic League, 1919-1923 (Box 19, Folder 195)
      New York City. Girls branch; general background information.
    - Recreation Foundation, 1923-1927 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - Rockefeller Surveys, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 197)
      Surveys of Metropolitan Museum of Art, American Museum of Natural History, and New York Public Library.
    - Sportsmanship Brotherhood, 1925-1926 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - Stryker's Lane Community Center, 1924-1925 (Box 19, Folder 199)
      Organization of clubs to give children of area an opportunity for recreation.
    - Torrey, Raymond, 1923-1924 (Box 19, Folder 200)
    - Traveler's Aid Society, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Brooklyn and Queens, 1918-1926 (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Brooklyn and Queens, 1918-1926 (Box 19, Folder 203)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Brooklyn and Queens - Pamphlets (Box 19, Folder 204)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Cleveland, 1919-1926 (Box 19, Folder 205)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago, 1924-1938 (Box 19, Folder 206)
      LSRM-RF. Investigations and research of Y activities. Professional school. Edward Jenkins.
      Photographs removed to RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1016, Box 2, Folder 19.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago, 1924-1938 (Box 19, Folder 207)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago, 1924-1938 (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Springfield, 1918-1928 (Box 19, Folder 209)
      LSRM-RF. Massachusetts. Physical education, expansion program, endowments, general background information. Lawrence Doggett, Herbert Pratt.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Springfield, 1918-1928 (Box 19, Folder 210)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Springfield, 1918-1928 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Springfield, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 212)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Springfield - Pamphlets (Box 20, Folder 213)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago - Reports (Box 20, Folder 214)
      Photographs.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago - Reports (Box 20, Folder 215)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) College - Chicago - Reports (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Foreign Born, 1921-1925 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - General Board - Foreign Division Survey, 1927-1932 (Box 20, Folder 218)
      LSRM-RF. Daniel J. Fleming.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - General Board - Foreign Division Survey, 1927-1932 (Box 20, Folder 219)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work, 1919-1929 (Box 21, Folder 220)
      Education Program, general background information. Edward Jenkins.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work, 1919-1929 (Box 21, Folder 221)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work, 1919-1929 (Box 21, Folder 222)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work - Reports (Box 21, Folder 223)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work - Reports (Box 21, Folder 224)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work - Reports (Box 21, Folder 225)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Foreign Work - Reports (Box 21, Folder 226)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Division - Home Work, 1919-1925 (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Division - Home Work, 1919-1925 (Box 22, Folder 228)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Division - Japan, 1923-1925 (Box 22, Folder 229)
      Reconstruction.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Merchant Seaman's Branch, 1922-1925 (Box 22, Folder 230)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - National Council, 1925-1929 (Box 22, Folder 231)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - National Council, 1925-1929 (Box 22, Folder 232)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - New York City, 1918-1929 (Box 22, Folder 233)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - New York City, 1918-1929 (Box 22, Folder 234)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - New York City - Pamphlets (Box 22, Folder 235)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Princeton in Peking, 1923-1924 (Box 23, Folder 236)
      Olin Wannamaker.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Retirement Fund, 1921-1926 (Box 23, Folder 237)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Silver Bay Association, 1921-1927 (Box 23, Folder 238)
      Conference grounds with other groups, boys' school.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Silver Bay Association, 1921-1927 (Box 23, Folder 239)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Silver Bay Association - Reports (Box 23, Folder 240)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Southern College, 1919-1929 (Box 23, Folder 241)
      LSRM-RF. Nashville, eventually a graduate school; training of leaders in South; general background information. W. D. Weatherford.
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Southern College, 1919-1929 (Box 23, Folder 242)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Tarrytown, 1918-1919 (Box 23, Folder 243)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Executive Committee, 1919-1923 (Box 23, Folder 244)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Executive Committee, 1924-1927 (Box 24, Folder 245)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Executive Committee - Pamphlets (Box 24, Folder 246)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Reports (Box 24, Folder 247)
    - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Reports (Box 24, Folder 248)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Brooklyn, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 249)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Brooklyn Industrial Girl, 1923-1927 (Box 24, Folder 250)
      Study of members and kinds of women employees; clubs and classes.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Cleveland, 1919-1920 (Box 24, Folder 251)
      Building fund.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1919-1934 (Box 24, Folder 252)
      LSRM-RF. General background information, special projects. Emma B. Speer.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1919-1934 (Box 24, Folder 253)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1919-1934 (Box 24, Folder 254)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - India, 1927-1929 (Box 25, Folder 255)
      Conference site.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Japan, 1923-1927 (Box 25, Folder 256)
      Restoration, building program.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Secretarial Retirement, 1920-1925 (Box 25, Folder 257)
      Annuity.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board - Reports (Box 25, Folder 258)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City, 1919-1929 (Box 25, Folder 259)
      LSRM-RF. Trowmart Inn, a residence for women. General background information, mortgage.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City, 1919-1929 (Box 25, Folder 260)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City, 1919-1929 (Box 25, Folder 261)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City - Studio Club, 1926-1928 (Box 25, Folder 262)
      Building.
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City - Pamphlets (Box 25, Folder 263)
    - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City - Reports (Box 25, Folder 264)
  - Appropriations - Child Study and Parent Education, 3_05
    - Albany Board of Education and Albany State Teachers College, 1930-1936 (Box 26, Folder 265)
      SF. Joint program, parent discussion groups. Albany Nursery School as a lab for observation and experiment including parents and teachers.
    - American Association for Adult Education, 1927-1931 (Box 26, Folder 266)
      LSRM-RF. Secretariat for Council on Parent Education. Edna White.
    - American Association for Education - Conference on Parent Education, 1928-1930 (Box 26, Folder 267)
      SF.
    - American Association of University Women, 1923-1931 (Box 26, Folder 268)
      LSRM-RF. Washington office, interest in child study; educational department.
    - American Association of University Women, 1923-1931 (Box 26, Folder 269)
    - American Home Economics Association, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 270)
    - American Home Economics Association - Child Development, 1929-1935 (Box 26, Folder 271)
      SF. Field work, consultation, research, conferences.
    - American Home Economics Association - Child Development, 1929-1935 (Box 26, Folder 272)
    - American Home Economics Association - Child Development, 1929-1935 (Box 26, Folder 273)
    - American Home Economics Association - Consulting Service, 1925-1929 (Box 26, Folder 274)
      Physical, mental, and emotional studies of children, advisory service.
    - American Home Economics Association - Washington Center, 1924-1927 (Box 26, Folder 275)
      LSRM-SF. Study and research on preschool child - joint effort of government and national groups.
    - American Home Economics Association - Washington Center, 1928-1935 (Box 27, Folder 276)
    - American Home Economics Association - Washington Center, 1928-1935 (Box 27, Folder 277)
    - American Home Economics Association - Reports (Box 27, Folder 278)
    - Bureau of Educational Experiments, 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 279)
      Tabulate and publish study results.
    - California Department of Education, 1925-1931 (Box 27, Folder 280)
      LSRM-SF. Secretary to organize and direct parent education experiment.
    - California Department of Education, 1925-1931 (Box 27, Folder 281)
    - Canadian National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 282)
      LSRM-SF. Laboratory and nursery schools; general background information, application of mental hygiene studies to school children.
    - "Child Life in New York City" - Barrows Survey - Report (Box 27, Folder 283)
    - Child Study Association - Conference on Parent Training, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 284)
    - Child Study Association - Extension Division, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 285)
      LSRM-SF. Editorial and training program, general background information, centers of study.
    - Child Study Association - Extension Division, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 286)
    - Child Study Association - Extension Division, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 287)
    - Child Study Association - Extension Division, 1934-1937 (Box 28, Folder 288)
    - Child Study Association - Study Groups, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 289)
    - Child Study Association - Teaching Materials, 1923-1926 (Box 28, Folder 290)
    - Child Study Association - Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 28, Folder 291)
    - Child Study and Parent Education - Reports (Box 28, Folder 292)
    - Child Study and Parent Education - Oklahoma, 1924-1927 (Box 28, Folder 293)
    - Child Study and Parent Training, 1923-1928 (Box 28, Folder 294)
    - Child Study Centers - North Carolina, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 295)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Clarke, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 296)
      LSRM-SF.
    - Child Study Fellowships - Goff, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 297)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Ibrahim, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 298)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Moissides, 1929-1931 (Box 28, Folder 299)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Muchow, 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 300)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Sanchez, 1927-1931 (Box 28, Folder 301)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Wolff, 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 302)
    - Child Study Fellowships (A-L) (Box 28, Folder 303)
    - Child Study Fellowships (M-Z) (Box 29, Folder 304)
    - Child Study Fellowships, 1924-1932 (Box 29, Folder 305)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Reports (Box 29, Folder 306)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Cincinnati, 1926-1928 (Box 29, Folder 307)